I was from a good family.
Because of his greed and his evil,
my family was ruined.
I was reduced to a demon for a hundred years.
How can I let it go?
To you,
did your husband really only leave you with hatred?
So what if there was?
What he did to me
cannot be made up for by any affection.
You only know the grudges in your heart,
but you don't understand the cause and effect.
Do you know
that you, your husband, and the maid
have been entangled for three lifetimes?
This ill-fated relationship could have ended in this life.
In the next life, you could have lived in peace
and spent a peaceful life.
But because of your hatred and delusion,
you fell into the demonic path
and cannot enter reincarnation.
And killed so many innocent people.
With your behavior,
the world will not forgive you.
The Way of Heaven
won't forgive you either.
Three lifetimes of ill-fated romance.
So what?
I don't care about past or future lives.
I only want satisfaction in this life.
Your sins are too deep,
and your obsession is too strong.
If you are unwilling to save yourself,
today I
will personally save you.
Sanshan Liujin Immortal,
we have been looking for you for a long time.
Seeing you today,
you are indeed extraordinary.
I may not be able to defeat you.
But my benefactor, Lady Tu,
might just be your match.
The Tu clan again.
You're also one of the Four Demons of the Tu Sect.
Ignorant child.
How do you know about the Four Demons of the Tu Sect?
Thunder Dragon has already been subdued by the master.
Don't be smug.
Among the Four Demons, Thunder Dragon and I have the weakest powers.
When we regroup and attack again,
we will make everyone in Er City
die with you.
We will meet again.
Who are you?
Lady Tu will avenge me.
It seems to be a misunderstanding.
The Golden Immortal of the Three Mountains.
Her Ladyship has found the Golden Immortal.
He killed Ruixi.
The town where Ruixi was located
is only a few dozen miles away from the Thunder Dragon's place.
There has been no news from the Thunder Dragon for several days.
It must be his doing too.
The Thunder Dragon and Ruixi are just worn-out shoes.
Helping me find the Golden Immortal
can be considered a complete merit.
I am willing to capture the Golden Immortal for Her Ladyship.
I am willing to go along.
You two have followed me for hundreds of years.
Although the Golden Immortal has lost his immortal body,
he is not that easy to deal with.
Don't let me down.
Yes, yes.
Thank you, immortal.
I thank you on behalf of the people of Ercheng.
No need for formalities, County Deputy.
Please get up.
And who are you?
Paying respects to my ancestor.
Who is your ancestor?
Hey, who are you?
You're so young, why are you claiming relatives randomly?
Forgive my rudeness.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I am a third-rank sorcerer of the Sitian Tower,
Hu San.
He's really an official from the Bureau of Astronomy.
A badge of the Bureau of Astronomy.
Who would dare to forge it?
Forgive my impoliteness.
Rise.
What does the Bureau of Astronomy do?
They belong to the imperial court.
They are like official monster catchers.
You are wrong about that, miss.
The Sitian Bureau observes celestial phenomena,
and establishes the calendar.
Above, we manage the destiny of the dynasty.
Below, we handle worldly disasters.
Catching demons is just something we do in passing.
Since Ercheng has been occupied by demons for so many years,
why didn't you come earlier?
Didn't I just say it?
There are simply too many things in this world
to manage.
There are countless demons all over the world.
And the people in the Sitian Bureau
are all one in a million
elites.
We really can't attend to everything.
However, logically speaking,
all these states and realms,
since the Sitian Bureau
placed Guanxin Mirrors in the government offices to guard them,
should have been protected.
I sent a pigeon to the capital for help.
But Ruixi is too capable.
She intercepts any message leaving the city.
This star mirror had already...
Country.
It seems the star mirrors everywhere need repairing.
I was ordered to go to Mount Leiting.
Rumor has it that monsters are causing trouble there.
But halfway there,
I saw a group of constables.
They told me
they ran into a monster at a country inn.
They also gave me a portrait.
Let me see it.
I reckon,
with your speed,
you should have arrived at Er City by now.
Constables.
Master,
it's those corrupt officials who want to rob our gold and silver.
Then what will you do?
Capture him?
The ancestor is a Golden Immortal descended to the mortal realm.
The dispute with the constables must be a misunderstanding.
I will report to the Sitian Tower to revoke the bounty,
and then apprehend the constables for interrogation.
Oh right,
the monster on Leiting Mountain
has already been eliminated by the two of us.
I admire your actions, ancestor.
I told you.
I am not your ancestor.
I cultivate the Hu family shamanic path.
You are the legendary Golden Immortal.
As far as I know,
you voluntarily descended to the mortal realm for some unknown reason.
But reincarnated as a Qingqiu demon fox.
In terms of seniority and experience,
you are my ancestor.
The Master is a demon?
Isn't he an immortal?
What does this mean?
Don't ask if you don't understand.
Who you are
has nothing to do with me.
You just said it yourself.
That demoness is backed by the great Tu demon.
They will surely come for revenge.
Since you are from the Sitian Bureau,
I'll leave the safety of this place to you.
Farewell.
Wait.
If you leave,
how will I report to His Majesty?
Are you trying to stop me?